[Music] there's
[Música]
a bomb there's some very bomb news
hay una bomba hay una novedad muy bomba
from Auro inemita would you make a woman
de Auro inemita la harías una mujer
never until I see her theme hand
jamás hasta que la vea tema manita
apart here she lets go I have some
aparte aquí se la suelta tengo unos
fingers that's why the girls come back [ __ ]
dedos por eso vuelven las chicas [__]
no we hadn't seen this place I have
no no habíamos visto esta lugar tengo
some fingers and he says wc that's why
unos dedos y le dice wc por eso vuelven
the girls come back no Regal reg what happens is that he did
las chicas no Regal reg lo que pasa es
n't understand a [ __ ] since his
que no entendió una [__] puesto que
voice was distorted I have some
tenía la voz distorsionada tengo unos
fingers the girls no but that what is oche what is it
dedos las chicas no pero eso qué es oche
in the squid game Juan a
que es en el juego del calamar Juan un
kiss baby Shark a new sipeo has emerged
beso baby Shark ha surgido un nuevo
with aurono attention Who's your
sipeo con aurono atención Quién es tu
friend friendo the handsome guy over there Yeah that handsome handsome
amigo amigoo el guapetón de allá Sí ese
And that I didn't take off my mask
guapetón Y eso que no me quit la máscara
I'll see you after this okay yeah yeah I'll
yo a ti te veo después de esto okay sí
be here a kiss
sí aquí estaré os falda un beso de
okay I'm paci introducing myself guys
acuerdo me estoy paci presentando chicos
When do the
Cuándo empieza los
games really start you can be in some
juegos de verdad me pedes ser unas
real situations you can be one
situaciones de verdad me pedes ser una
The dad already said I already
Ya dijo el pap Ya
said no Hey it's them say yes it
dijo yo no Oye que son ellas di sí que
's true me I'm here quiet
es verdad yo yo estoy aquí quieto
silent it's that I'm not I feel
callado es que yo no soy me siento
intimacy And  this doesn't end here we have
intimidad Y esto no queda aquí tenemos
more interactions with this
más interacciones con esta chica
Mysterious girl put it there I know that the
Misteriosa ponle ahí yo que sé a la
lasagna should be a little spicy but not that either Yes
lasaña que pique tantito pero tampoco
yes I understand something suggestive but
que a Sí sí entiendo algo sugerente pero
not too correct and with all due respect
no demasiado correcto y con todo respeto
in the world of course Okay well I think that at
del mundo claro Okay pues yo creo que en
this moment I must be blind because I
este momento debo de estar ciega porque
don't see your message telling me to
no veo tu mensaje diciéndome que nos
meet
veamos
now one for auron please like that
ahora uno para auron por favor así igual
one for me please with the same the
uno para mí por favor con con la misma
same level with the same level Yes yes
el mismo nivel con el mismo nivel Sí sí
you also like something slightly
también te gusta algo ligeramente
suggestive Yes yes the same level is very
sugerente Sí sí el mismo nivel está muy
good your only defect auron is that you don't
bien tu único defecto auron es que no
wake up with me Uy uyu damn lucky we
despiertas conmigo Uy uyu [__] suerte
told her a bit of salsa
que le hemos dicho un soque de salsa
Valentina [ __ ] if we tell her the whole
valentina [__] si le decimos todo el
bottle and you'll say no she also
bote y diréis no a Comanche también le
said something to Comanche Yes and she also
ha dicho cosita Sí y a Comanche también
put these tweets to Comanche the twist I was
le ha puesto estos tweet lo twist yo era
Rodolfa kangaroo new achievement unlocked
rodolfa cangura nuevo logro desbloqueado
give a personal compliment to auron check
hacerle un piropo personal a auron check
Dani from the past that you watched her videos when you were
Dani del pasado que veías sus videos con
14 This was for you It was a pleasure having
14 años Esto fue por ti Fue un placer
served you this afternoon  auron Play
haberte atendido esta tarde auron Play
I hope that searching for interaction with
Espero que buscando la interacción con
someone, let's see this house pairing no I mean
algún a ver está casa pareando no O sea
experience enjoying this edition has
experiencia disfrutando de esta edición
been the best my service for now
haya sido la mejor mi servicio por ahora
has ended but I would appreciate it if you
ha terminado pero Te agradecería si
fill out our satisfaction survey
llenas nuestra encuesta de satisfacción
because for my part I have had a
porque de mi parte Me la he pasado muy
great time Who is I don't know who it is as
bien Quién es no sé quién es como
added to Ur Play has followed her Hey
agregado a Ur Play la ha seguido Oye
queto you don't have to mean anything
queto no tienes por qué significar nada
but since she supposedly returned with
pero como supuestamente ha vuelto con
Gemita people are speculating well there is
gemita la gente anda especulando pues
a bomb eh There is a bomb there is a
hay una bomba eh Hay una bomba hay una
bomb wait let's see this first
bomba espera vamos a ver primero esto
grandpa Your only defect is that your
abuelo Tu único defecto es que te crecen
dwarfs grow let's see let's see let's see let's see the
enanos veamos veamos veamos veamos los
new rumors of auron and Gemita
nuevos rumores de auron y de gemita
seen in a movie theater Okay let's see This is
vistos en un cine Okay a ver Esto es
false let's see I haven't seen anything yet but
falso a ver aún no he visto nada pero
I want to think that it is false because I do not
quiero pensar que es falso porque yo no
believe that after everything that has
me creo que después de todo lo que ha
happened he makes it so obvious
pasado lo haga tan evidente poco lo
we saw little of it not a little we saw it no good It turns out
vimos no poco lo vimos no bueno Resulta
that in the Instagram stories of
ser que en las historias de Instagram de
November 22, 24 aur Yes well
el 22 de noviembre del 24 aur Sí bueno
in this case it is false But not
en este caso sí es falso Pero no por
because Ho Because after everything that
porque Ho Porque después de todo lo que
happened I don't know what but I mean yes yes I already
pasó no sé qué pero o sea si si ya lo
we recently saw her come back And let
vimos hace poco volver Y dejarla que
her upload stories in the car and
ella subiera historias en el coche y
stuff I'm going to a movie theater Now this
demás vo voy en un cine Ya esta
post here and next to it there's a
publicación aquí y al lado hay una
person in white No yeah and curiously
persona de blanco No ya y curiosamente
eh apparently gemita on some occasion
eh por lo visto gemita en alguna ocasión
apparently she has also published a
por lo visto ha publicado también una
photo eh in white no this is from the
foto eh de blanco no esto de la cuenta
@info gemita account let's see that photo is not it's not
@info gemita a ver esa foto no es no es
from today eh info let's see info gemita let's see
de hoy eh info a ver info gemita a ver
if this account here info Ita that photo
si esta cuenta de aquí info Ita esa foto
dressed in white is old I don't see it as
vestida de blanco es antigua no la veo
recent So no That's not it
que sea reciente Así que no Esa no es
either I don't know what day it is it doesn't say the
tampoco no sé de qué día es no dice la
date the thing is that people have said
fecha la cosa es que la gente ha dicho
Hey look auron has gone to the movies there's a
Oye mira auron ha ido al cine hay una
person in white Maybe it's Gema and
persona vda de blanco Será que es Gema y
I say bro it could be anyone it
yo digo bro puede ser cualquier persona
could even be a friend but well the
puede ser hasta un amigo pero bueno lo
first thing that comes to mind is gemita No and
primero que se les ocurre es gemita No y
this is responding to a post that said
esto respondiendo a un post que decía
yesterday apparently auroplay ended its
ayer al parecer auroplay terminó su
relationship with gemita because she cheated on him again
relación con gemita porque lo volvió a
no this is from him 21 damn a
engañar no esto es de el 21 [__] un
post with 4 million likes 76000 likes
post con 4 millones de likes 76000 likes
what the [ __ ]
qué [__]
76,000 likes on the post to the mother mother and
76,000 likes de post a la madre madre y
people comment but the photos are not
la gente comenta pero las fotos no son
from the same day no I don't know they passed them to me
del mismo día no no sé me las pasaron
well well well well I think she's not
bueno bueno bueno bueno creo que no te
answering you I think that when they went to the
responde yo creo que cuando fueron al
cupra they were there she must have been there for a few
cupra sí estaban habrá estado unas
weeks and then something must have happened again
semanas y luego otra vez habrá pasado
here one puts one but if she is
algo aquí le pone uno pero si ella está
in Barcelona at least she has a
en Barcelona al menos que tenga una
twin and they are in two different places okay well let's
gemela y esté dos lugares distintos ya
see auron could be in
bueno a ver auron puede estar en
Barcelona perfectly Whenever you want
Barcelona perfectamente Cuando quiera
come guys it wasn't gemita it wasn't gemita
ven chicos no era gemita no era gemita
eye but a person comes here below and
ojo pero viene aquí una persona abajo y
says she's in Andorra she uploaded this this
dice está en andorra esto lo subió esta
morning and yesterday she uploaded a photo of her
mañana y ayer subió una foto de su
kitten let's see It's that the photo I don't know I do
gatito a a ver Es que la foto yo no sé
n't follow gemita much okay And Javi is
no sigo mucho a gemita vale Y Javi tiene
40 years old mura already and he leaves the chime and looks for a
40 tacos mura ya y deja el chime y busca
job Why did he make a video
trabajo Por qué ha hecho un vídeo
scratching me now he doesn't put
rascando de mí ahora bien Él no pone
names if surnames he talks like that you are
nombres si apellidos él habla así tienes
34 years old dude really if you are over
34 años tío de verdad si tienes más de
30 you shouldn't have a
30 años no deberías tener un canal de
gossip channel what the [ __ ] are you doing talking about the
salseo qué [__] haces hablando de la
squidcraft games controversy well cap it You
polémica de los squidcraft games pues
know what I do talk  putting
capa Sabes qué Yo sí hablo poniendo
names and surnames and I'm going to talk about you
nombres y apellidos y voy a hablar de ti
in this video about what you've said about me
en este vídeo de lo que has dicho de mí
and also I'm going to tell you something
y también además voy a contaros una
interesting because lately there are so many
curiosidad porque últimamente hay tantos
content creators who attack
creadores de contenido que atacan a los
gossip channels I'm going to explain it to you
canales de salseo os lo voy a explicar
in this video but first as I say
en este vídeo pero antes como os digo
Always good this time says it
Siempre bueno en esta ocasión lo dice
capa and before continuing with the gossip Don't
capa y antes de seguir con el salseo No
forget to follow me to always
te olvides de seguirme para siempre
be informed of the latest gossip
estar informado de los últimos salseos
because you've already heard it following for
pues ya lo habéis oído seguiendo para
more gossip let's go Point by point first
más salseo vamos Punto por punto primero
capa messes with my age I'm 34 years old I
capa se mete con mi edad tengo 34 años
don't hide it on any social network there
no lo oculto en ninguna red social
should be a law that prohibits
debería haber una ley que prohíba a la
people over 30 from creating
gente de más de 30 años hacerse cuentas
tiktok accounts to talk about gossip about
de tiktok para hablar sobre cotilleos de
influencer couples well well well
parejas de influencers bueno bueno bueno
guys eh zip zip and zip zop caught
chicos eh zip zip y zip zop pillados
walking hand in hand down the street guys
andando de la mano por la calle chicos
Welcome to gossip glip glob and glab
Bienvenidos a salseo glip glob y glab
glab have announced their breakup you are
glab han han anunciado su ruptura tienes
34 years old dude Why are you talking about whether
34 años tío Por qué estás hablando de si
two teenagers are a couple now what are
dos adolescentes son pareja ahora qué
you going to do are you going to inspect  the
vas a hacer tú vas a fiscalizar el
content on social networks you are going to
contenido en las redes sociales vas a
say what can and cannot be
decir lo que se puede y lo que no se
done And from what age it can be
puede hacer Y a partir de qué edad se
done and not according to What thing
puede hacer y no según Qué cosa me
seems so absurd to me the issue of age
parece tan absurdo el tema de la edad
What happens that when Before there were magazines
Qué pasa que cuando Antes había revistas
like super pop or loca dedicated to
como super pop o loca dedicada a los
teenagers and they talked about
adolescentes y que hablaban de
teenagers who made those magazines
adolescentes quién hacía esas revistas
what teenage journalist not older people
qué periodist adolescente no gente más
also I find the
mayor además me hace mucho gracia lo del
age issue very funny because who manages the
tema de la edad porque quién lleva las
social networks of people like you, people teenagers
redes sociales de personas como tú gente
or older people Who are the ones
adolescente o gente mayor Quiénes son
who invest in content for people like you,
los que invierten en contenido de gente
people teenagers or older people
como tú gente adolescente o gente mayor
what idiot escapes eh I swear I mean it's the
qué tonto escapa eh Te lo juro o sea es
dumbest thing there is eh Let's see Good
de lo más tonto que hay eh A ver Buen
point because as if let's see Gemita is not going to be
punto porque como si a ver gemita no va
able to go from Barcelona to Andorra in
a poder irse de Barcelona a andorra en
one day or less bro by
un día o en menos bro en
car it won't take long bro it is a
auto no tardará mucho bro es un país
big country so it is possible that this person there
grande entonces posible que esta persona
are some possibilities but I want to
hay unas posibilidades pero yo quiero
think not and I think we all Also we
pensar que no y creo que todos También
want to think not true is that yes
queremos pensar que no verdad es que si
yes it is Gema Auron is already there no no but I
si es Gema Ya auron está no no pero yo
want to think no what do you answer
quiero pensar que no qué le responden
So Auron is not doing Stream
Entonces auron no está haciendo Stream
because she is doing the  of chauffeur so as not to be
porque está haciendo el de chófer para
careless and leave with another
no descuidar y que se vaya con otro
gemita no no no don't say those things bro
gemita no no no no digan esas cosas bro
I want to think that this can't be
quiero pensar que es que no puede estar
happening friends it can't be
pasando esto amigos no puede estar
happening the closures are not the same well
pasando los cierres no son iguales bueno
total this is denied not that this photo
total esto se desmiente no que esta foto
was G half they are not in the same fabric I think
fuera G mitad no son en la misma tela
not deo I think I saw around there look
creo no deo creo que vi por ahí mira
here here for the brother to say something
aquí aquí para el hermano decir que algo
amente insult him friend please already bro already already
amente insultarlo amigo por favor ya bro
my Already my son already My son already
ya ya mi Ya mi hijo ya Ya mi hijo ya por
please what's going on There What's going on What's going on
favor qué pasa Ahí Qué pasa Qué pasa
green it's not her nor is she going to do it
verdo no es ella ni lo va a hacer
continue okay There we had the brother who has
proseguir vale Ahí teníamos al hermano
n't commented on this one in the
que eso no lo ha comentado este del
video we didn't have the brother commenting on
vídeo no teníamos al hermano comentando
the subject that no that it's not her and
el tema de que no de que no es ella y
that she's not going to do it no As much as I
que ni lo va a hacer no Por más que
try to turn it around but Juanito has
intente darle la vuelta pero Juanito ha
published this t Okay bombshell auron Play
publicado este t Okay bombazo auron Play
separated again from gemita Why
separado otra vez de gemita Por qué
Because since apparently they weren't
Porque como por lo visto no eran
official yet she cheated on him again even if
oficiales aún lo volvió a engañar aunque
you don't believe it I sent
usted no lo crea le he mandado un
Juanito a WhatsApp to ask him
WhatsApp a Juanito para preguntarle que
what Ed is the one he has and
que qué Ed es la que tiene y no
I didn't find it funny seeing vin
me me ha hecho gracia ver vín
answering the tweet no eh but of course
contestando al twit no eh pero claro en
based on what I mean but let's see clear It's that
base a qué O sea pero a ver claro Es que
Juanito posted this he hasn't
esto lo ha puesto Juanito no ha vuelto a
tweeted anything else not praise and he's been
twitear más nada no loar y se ha quedado
so Pancho I mean this is what
tan Pancho o sea esto lo ha puesto
Juanito posted he hasn't tweeted anything else and he's been
Juanito no ha vuelto twitear más nada y
so Pancho I
se ha quedado tan Pancho yo le he
asked him Javi what do you think they
preguntado Javi tú qué piensas que
broke up or not Let's see I think so eh
terminaron o no A ver yo pienso que sí
But not because I don't know if because I
eh Pero no por no sé si porque le haya
cheated on him again because it didn't even
engañado otra vez porque ni siquiera
work out but they
haya llegado a cuajar sino que
were seeing each other for a few days at
estuvieron viendo durante unos días en
that time I'm going of course you remember that
aquel momento voy claro os acordáis que
Auron said that in a few weeks when
auron dijo lo de en unaas semanas cuando
I get it straight I'll tell you something well let's see
me aclare os digo algo pues a loj a ver
this comes from somewhere no I mean it's that
esto sale de alguna parte no o sea es
suddenly people start
que esto de repente que empieza la gente
commenting let's see if yes how that
a comentar ver si si cóm que se
Fede the ad is called that he left He left
Fede el ad se llama que se fue Se fue
for 100 million not in the rosle haem we
por 100 millones no en el rosle haem
see some other little thing family or what did I
vemos alguna cosilla más familia o qué
put something else in the title that we
puse algo más en el título que no
haven't commented on Air no I haven't left
hayamos comentado Air no no me dejado
anything out to comment no
nada por comentar no puse nada en el
I put nothing in the title that I have left uncommented on Let's see, pass me the link to the clips luar and we put it in this extract Let's see, pass me the clicks, let's see Where does what Lu says come from? The thing about Auron comes from these clicks because after words said in his
click porque tras palabras dichas en su
last Stream, people suspect that
último Stream la gente sospecha que
Gemita had cheated on him again It is
gemita lo habría vuelto a engañar Es
evident that Auron was trying to
evidente que auron estaba intentando
get back with Gemita, that's why the kin thing,
volver con gemita por eso lo de la kin
but now according to everything, today he was
pero ahora según con tod hoy tenía
planning to leave this weekend but
pensado irse el fin de semana pero
things happened Ah, it's just that with so many lies I'll eat them
pasaron cosas Ah es que de tanta mentira
all now you I'll eat them
Ya me las como todas tú me las como
all you I put this on Twitter what
todas tú esto lo puse yo en Twitter que
made like the joke not that he ate the
hizo como la broma no de que se comió el
Ricky thing, he didn't eat the bite
tema de Ricky no se comió el el bite
this that Ricky made, not with the
este que hizo Ricky no con lo de un
fake event thing, well I've also eaten
evento falso pues me he comido también
Ricky's it's not It's that no no I don't
la de Ricky no es Es que no no no
learn you of course I understood it as a
aprendo tú claro Yo lo entendí como una
joke because of his thing with Gemita, not because
broma por lo suyo con gemita no por lo
of Cook and so on, but no I didn't assume
de Cook y demás pero no no di por hecho
that it was something current I don't learn
que se tratase de algo actual no aprendo
you I don't learn Joan it's an incredible thing
tú no aprendo Joan es una cosa increíble
you are  that I eat even the one from up to up to she
tú es que me me me como hasta la de
deceives me Ricky eddy you this
hasta hasta me engaña Ricky edy tú esto
already what the [ __ ] is this This is a
ya qué [__] es esto Esto es una cosa
wonderful thing you already fool me Ricky Eddie
maravillosa ya me engañas a Ricky Eddie
you ah you fool me Ricky Eddie Ah it's that
tú ah me engañas a Ricky Eddie Ah es que
with so many lies I already eat them all you I eat them
de tanta mentira Ya me las como todas tú
all you have
me las como todas tú me he comido
also eaten Ricky's edit It's not that no no I don't
también la de Ricky edit No es que no no
learn you don't learn you don't learn
no aprendo tú no aprendo tú no aprendo
Joan it's an incredible thing you it's that I eat
Joan es una cosa increíble tú es que me
even the one from up to up she
me me como hasta la de hasta hasta me
deceives me Ricky Ed you this already what the [ __ ] is
engaña Ricky Ed tú esto ya qué [__] es
this but there's something else Eh luare there's something
esto pero hay algo más Eh luare hay algo
else because it says there he planned to make
más porque ahí dice tuvo planeado hacer
plans he was going to make plans for the
planes iba a hacer planes el fin de
weekend but for whatever reason it hasn't happened
semana pero por lo que sea no ha pasado
something else is said aurun's brother
se dice algo más el hermano de aurun
confirms it's not that he has to do it
confirma no es que tenga por qué hacerlo
but as the largest account of gossip he
pero como mayor cuenta de salseos
confirms 100% that aurun was not at
confirma al 100% que aurun no estaba en
the cinema with her I agree with you
el cine con ella de acuerdo contigo
Antonio a kiss pan me period he deceives
Antonio un beso pan me punto engaña
even Ricky edit I mean any [ __ ] he
hasta Ricky edit o sea cualquier [__]
deceives me By the way the one with glasses says
me engaña Por cierto le dice el gafas
this face revolvi ose laughing I
este cara revolvi ose de la risa me
loved the cinema of the point boss I don't  I think
encantó cine del punto patrón yo no creo
a kiss georgio But I don't think it has
que un beso georgio Pero yo no creo que
anything to do with it eh Let's see bombshell
tenga nada que ver eh A ver bombazo
confirmed 100% auron and gemita
confirmado al 100% auron y gemita no
are not together but they have not broken up their
están juntos pero tampoco han roto su
relationship either because they never officially gave each other a
relación porque jamás se dieron una
second chance
segunda oportunidad de forma oficial
now auron could be a candidate for giga
ahora auron podría ser aspirante a giga
and gemita continue doing it m Of course of course it's not that they have Of course it's
y gemita seguir haciendolo m Claro claro
not that they have
no es que hayan claro no es que hayan
broken up it's not that they have broken up It's just that what
roto no es que hayan roto Es que lo que
happens is that
pasa es que ellos se fueron a Oh no la
they went to Oh no the account who is e It's just that what happens is that they saw each other again they would be hooking up they would be whatever not whatever and they never came back of course how do you read it dude how do you read it and as for everything that's
ustedes y en cuanto a todo lo que está
going on Well the truth is that I don't
pasando Pues la verdad es que no me
feel like talking much about the subject if I tell you
apetece hablar mucho del tema si te digo
if I'm completely honest To me I do
si soy completamente sincera A mí hace
n't know a few years ago they told me the
no sé unos años me cuentan la situación
current situation and I don't believe anything plan You know
actual y no me creo nada plan Sabes Me
everything seems so surreal to me and everything is so
parece todo tan surrealista y todo tan
crazy and everything is so I don't know everything makes me so
loco y todo tan no sé me da todo tanta
sad and I don't know I just wish with all my heart that they
pena y no sé solo deseo de corazón que
are well that everyone is well and I
estén bien que todo el mundo esté bien y
wish the best but I don't know  I feel sorry for
deseo lo mejor pero no sé me da me da
everything I don't know everything is very surreal I
pena todo No sé todo muy surrealista yo
feel like I'm living like some
siento que estoy viviendo como una
kind of strange situation you know
especie de de situación extraña sabes
everything is very strange but well I wish for the best I do
todo muy raro pero bueno deseo lo mejor
n't know Well honestly I think that's where
no s Pues sinceramente yo creo que que
things are going eh I'm going to try to
van por ahí los tiros eh voy a intentar
give it a spin and we're going to try
darle una vuelta y vamos a intentar esta
tonight to find out something more but what I
noche averiguar algo más pero a mí lo
feel is that there was an approach
que me da es que hubo una acercamiento
he would surely fall but in terms of a roll
él caería seguramente pero en tema rollo
in a roll no and and she well let's
en tema un rollete no y y ella pues a
see they didn't get back together officially and she
ver no volvieron de forma oficial y ella
well it would be busy no I don't know that's what
pues sería movida no no sé es lo que
I think the last screw Well I think
creo yo el último polvito Bueno yo creo
that I even see him capable of being in the
que incluso lo veo capaz a es de de
middle of getting hooked and and and wanting maybe let's
medio que engancharse y y y querer a lo
see if he falls if something more comes out
mejor a ver si cae si surge algo más
okay but but I don't think it's clear that it's like
vale pero pero no creo que claro ser así
Juanito is saying it
tal cual como lo está diciendo Juanito
in the tweet I don't know what he's referring to let's see they
en el twit no sé a qué se refiere a ver
tell me that Auron's brother
me dicen que el hermano de auron
denied that in a TT What was Auron's brother's tweet What was
desmintió eso en un TT Cómo era el twit
Auro's brother's tweet we'll call him
del hermano de Auro ya le llamaremos
How is he we'll call him zero we'll
Cómo es el ya le llamaremos cero ya le
call him zero yeah  that we have seen
llamaremos cero a sí lo que hemos visto
he confirms that let's see but he
él confirma de que a ver pero él
confirms that she has not been there let's see
confirma que ella no ha estado ahí a ver
what he is confirming is that he has
lo que él está confirmando es que que él
not gone with her to the movies but eh He does not
no ha ido con ella al cine pero eh No
confirm anything of, I mean he does not even
confirma nada de o sea ni siquiera
insinuate anything that he could have because
insinúa nada de que haya podido porque
I think that the brother would not cut himself and he
yo creo que el hermano no se cortaría y
would be very pissed off if if there had
estaría muy [__] si si hubiera
been another deception he would not have thrown her
habido otro engaño no la hubiera tirado
no So why, why hide
no Entonces para qué para qué ocultar
that, I mean I think that I think that
eso o sea yo creo que yo creo que la
Auro's joke of this day of [ __ ] me
broma de Auro de de este día de [__] me
fools even Ricky Eddie I think that it is
engaña hasta Ricky Eddie Yo creo que es
em making reference to Gemita's horns
em haciendo referencia a los cuernos de
no and that he has cheated on her two or
gemita no y que la ha engañado dos o
three times eh but but currently
tres veces eh pero pero no actualmente
in the last few days I mean I think that I
en los últimos días O sea yo creo que yo
think that it has been Well I know levino
creo que que ha sido Pues yo sé levino
the exist well they put it bouncing I do not
el exist bien se lo pusieron rebotando
know the truth I do not know the truth I am going to
no sé la verdad no sé la verdad voy a
try to find out there to see if I
intentar averiguar por ahí a ver si me
find out something but yes it seems very
entero de algo pero sí que me parece muy
strange to me that Juanito Launches to put that
raro que Juanito se Lance a poner eso
without anything no I mean like there is not
sin sin nada no O sea en plan es que ni
even rumor okay
siquiera hay rumor vale
[Music]
[Música]